I don't have an extra!
I know, right?
I'm a meat eater, aren't I?
I like to tinker with the members.
What?
Well...
But it does make sense.
I've never heard of hot air.
It's so much better than the video.
It's so crazy.
How do you say it?
Hot wind?
Shay's eyes...
You know...
They look like Shay's.
Shay's eyes.
So, this is what I'm talking about.
The kettle and the idol
Here they come!
It's the kettle of the Stardust cow and the kettle of the secret stand!
It's amazing, today we've already jumped over the walls of the office
Here she is, our idol!
Please come in!
I'm Kanon, the Kyushu girl.
Ontoshi is 20 years old!
Yes, 20 years old.
From Kyushu?
Yes, I am.
Thank you very much.
May I ask you what kind of group Kyushu Joshi Yakuza is?
Yes, first of all, Kyushu Joshi Yakuza
Aggressive dance and all-live vocal work.
And the most attractive point is their soulful and passionate live performance.
I debuted last March.
Before that, when I was an idol, I saw Kyushu Joshi Role live for the first time.
They were so cool, I was bowled over.
You were bowled over?
Yes, I did.
And you joined the group in March?
Yes, that's right.
Before that, when you saw them?
Yes, sir.
And you were surprised that there was such a cool group in Kyushu?
I was really surprised. I love cool idols.
I love cool idols, so I'm very happy to be a part of Kyushu Girls.
And now, the show opens in Japan on April 8.
I heard that a new member has joined the group.
We have a new member!
How many members did you have before?
Up until now, we were four.
We were a group of four.
Now we are a group of five, is that correct?
Yes, that's right.
What kind of new members did you have?
None of them have any experience in the game.
We have a really, really new member who has no experience in games.
We are now a five-member team.
I also joined the Kyushu Girls last year.
I joined the Kyushu Girls last year and spent about a month or two choreographing songs and working hard for my debut.
I was working hard to make my debut.
I saw many of the new members overlap with me from a year ago, and I'm accepting their efforts.
I hope that the five of us will work hard together from now on.
I'm looking forward to seeing you play the role of the Kyushu girls in the future.
There's no doubt that they're going to be more powerful than ever.
Tsubasa is still Tsubasa.
Tsubasa is the Kyushu Joshi actor Tsubasa...
The wings...
You could say they're five wings.
New wings!
New wings have been added?
I see.
So this is the first time
This is the first time she's appeared in a program outside of the idol division of StarPlastdad Promotions.
She will be appearing at an event called "Tokyo Yakan Land" on June 6 at Harajuku Ruido.
We also asked her to appear at an event called Tokyo Yakan Land on June 6 at Harajuku Ruido, and it was decided.
Thank you very much.
What do you think?
He's such a cute idol.
Please come for the second time!
I still don't understand the concept of this event.
I'd like you to be a part of the second event.
We'd like to have her participate in the second event as well.
We'd love to have you.
What did you think when you heard about this?
At first, I was so happy that Starda invited me to play the role of a Kyushu girl in their event.
When I was asked if I would like to play the role of Hanae-chan there, I was very happy. I wasn't sure if I was the right person for the role at first.
I wasn't sure if I was the right choice at first.
I wanted more people to know me as Hanon and as the Kyushu girl, and I wanted to do my best.
I also felt that I wanted to do my best.
I hope I can absorb a lot of things here and connect it to my personal growth.
I'm very excited right now!
The catch copy is "Tenshi na Koi Sweet Tree", which is a catch copy for idols.
The catchphrase of an idol.
This show is called
Kokoro-san
Militant Gorilla-chan
Mr. Can
Blue Hawaii
Mako-chan
Thank you very much for your support!
Thank you very much!